

ANNA KOVALOVA

DETAILS

<u>akannka@gmail.com</u> +380664576803

PROFILE

I have analytical thinking and ingenuity in solving non-standard problems. I have been programming for 4 years and I have already had some skills. I am fond of learning languages: my English level is B2 and now I am learning German. I have learned Java, Python, C++, Javascript and I am interested in web development lately.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Java-developer

JUNE 2019 - AUGUST 2019

Make Android projects with team

Interpreter

JUNE 2021 - JULY 2021

Translation of scientific papers related to programming

Interpreter

AUGUST 2021 - DECEMBER 2021

Work with English text/audio to learn a program that helps in online meetings (writes text, recognizes sentences, highlights tasks, / deadlines / problems that need urgent solution, etc.)

Web developer

JUNE 2021

Make web-sites for clients

EDUCATION

Kakhovka Educational Complex "Gymnasium - Specialized School of I Degree with Advanced Study of Foreign Languages" of Kakhovka City Council of Kherson Oblast

SEPTEMBER 2008 - MAY 2019

Java training

NOVEMBER 2017 - MAY 2018

The training program is adapted to the requirements of the certification exam of Oracle Corporation

HTML Academy

JUNE 2021 - JUNE 2021

Interactive online courses

Codifun

DECEMBER 2018 - MAY 2019

WOW Teachers

APRIL 2019 - JUNE 2019

WOW Teachers is an all-Ukrainian social and educational project for the free teaching of computer science and senior pupils on the basics of web development

Taras Shevchenko National University of Kyiv

SEPTEMBER 2019 - JUNE 2023

Student of Taras Shevchenko National University of Kyiv, Faculty of Computer Science and Cybernetics, System Analysis, Department of Applied Statistics

EPAM University Programm

APRIL 2021 - AUGUST 2021

Front-End Spring 2021

LINKS

My porfolio - https://akannka.github.io/portfolio/

SKILLS

Leadership and Teamwork Critical thinking and problem solving

Communication Skills Computer Skills

Problem Solving Creativity

Fast Learner Ability to Work in a Team

Ability to Work Under Pressure Adaptability

LANGUAGES

English(B2) Ukrainian

Russian

HOBBIES

Dancing, yoga, reading, badminton.